<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>MMg on LS | Papermod</title>
    <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/tags/mmg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MMg on LS | Papermod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/tags/mmg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Grandpa&#39;s Poison Out</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/adude7979/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/adude7979/</guid>
      <description>A six year old girl lends her sick grandfather her hand, and then more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Sex With Little Girls</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6289/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6289/</guid>
      <description>This is the 50th and final episode of my pedo ring series. &amp;#39;The Pedo Ring Series Summary of Episodes&amp;#39;, under my name, gives the full order. To understand the reference to some characters in this episode, it is best to read at least the 2 before it. Please don&amp;#39;t be put off by the &amp;#39;nosex&amp;#39; tag here - there is much reference and imagery of it, and things going on behind the scenes. There is important erotic plot developmental which the &amp;#39;thinking&amp;#39; type of pedosexual should enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wanted: Child-Sex</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6062/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6062/</guid>
      <description>This is episode 45 in the Ring series. It can be read alone but would be best to read at least 42-44 first, which give the full lead in. All the episodes are loosely linked by the central premise of a pedo ring (see &amp;#39;summary of episodes&amp;#39; for full order). Here we follow the progress of central members Dan, a 32yo teacher of the 10yo Hannah, and career pedos Simon and Anthony, together with one little ethnic girl who has not been seen for many episodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice Bit of Asian Child-Sex</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6047/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6047/</guid>
      <description>This is episode 44 in the Ring series. It can be read alone but would be best to read at least 41-43 first, which give the full lead in. All the episodes are loosely linked by the central premise of a pedo ring (see&amp;#39;summary of episodes&amp;#39; for full order). 35yo Sean here is the central male character, stepdad to the extremely sexed 10yo Hannah, living with her Mom Michelle who has long since known he only wanted her for&amp;#39;access&amp;#39; to the child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Sexual Experiences For 9yo Elise</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5877/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5877/</guid>
      <description>This is episode 40 in the Ring series. It can be enjoyed separately. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the sexual molesting of her now 10yo daughter, Hannah. Over time, 8 other men have come into her life, and 4 other girls have featured. A new one is being inducted tonight...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 7-Year-Old Treasure</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5544/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5544/</guid>
      <description>This is story 36 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the sexual molesting of her then 9yo daughter, Hannah. Over time, 7 other men have come into her life, two of whom being his good friend Simon, and Anthony. The latter specializes in &amp;#39;little&amp;#39; girls, and has another to offer...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spit-Roast Night For 10yo Hannah</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5262/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5262/</guid>
      <description>This is story 33 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a useless single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the complete sexual molesting of her attractive 10yo daughter, Hannah. Since then, 7 others have got involved, the earliest being 32yo schoolteacher Dan, who is smitten with her. 37yo Simon &amp;#39;likes&amp;#39; her too, in his way, and he and Sean have a &amp;#39;spit-roast&amp;#39; planned...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Extremely Unripe and Exotic Delicacy</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4830/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4830/</guid>
      <description>This is story 23 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a useless single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the complete sexual molesting of her dau 9yo Hannah. Over time, Dan (32) who is Hannah&amp;#39;s schoolteacher has joined in, as has his old friend 65yo Bill, and an old pedo buddy of Sean&amp;#39;s - 37yo Simon. Now Simon and Sean have concluded a deal with an old pedo contact, Anthony, for regular exchanges of Hannah with a 6yo ethnic girl named Camelia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale Of Two Little Girls&#39; Sex-Lives</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4695/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4695/</guid>
      <description>This is part 19 in the Pedophile Ring series. 9yo Hannah has been taken on holiday by her schoolteacher/abuser, Dan. Meanwhile Sean and his hard-edged pedo buddy, Simon, finish off a nasty little abduction and rape of 10yo Abigail, stepgranddaughter of Bill (the 3rd of Hannah&amp;#39;s abusers). Now, with Hannah back home with a stepdad (Sean) who &amp;#39;loves her in a manner of speaking&amp;#39;, status quo is resumed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abducting Nice 10yo Abigail</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4675/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4675/</guid>
      <description>This is part 17 in the Pedophile Ring series. 9yo Hannah is taking a break from the story for a while, as she has been taken on holiday by her schoolteacher/abuser, Dan. Here Sean and his hard-edged pedo buddy, Simon, carry out their abduction of Abigail, stepgranddaughter of Bill (the 3rd of Hannah&amp;#39;s abusers). Can be read from here, but makes more sense if you have followed the previous stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning For Sweet Innocent Abigail</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4674/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4674/</guid>
      <description>This is part 16 of the Pedophile Ring series. 9yo Hannah is taking a break from the story for a while, as she has been taken on holiday by her schoolteacher/abuser, Dan. Here Sean and his hard-edged pedo buddy, Simon, discuss the abduction of the innocent 10yo Abigail, stepgranddaughter of Bill (the 3rd of Hannah&amp;#39;s abusers). Complicated? A bit, but makes more sense if you have followed the previous stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rape Of Abigail</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4676/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4676/</guid>
      <description>This is part 18 in the Pedophile Ring series. 9yo Hannah is taking a break from the story for a while, as she has been taken on holiday by her schoolteacher/abuser, Dan. Here Sean and his hard-edged pedo buddy, Simon, are carrying out their planned abduction and rape of Abigail, stepgranddaughter of Bill (the 3rd of Hannah&amp;#39;s abusers). They have her in a clearing, in the woods, having already forced her to strip and subjected her to fondling and kissing and cowed her by threats, which was not difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan Returns For More Of Little Hannah</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4626/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4626/</guid>
      <description>This is the 8th part of the Paedophile Ring series. Sean is a 35yo guy who lives with a single Mum, for the purpose of sexually abusing her pretty 9yo daughter. A few days ago he invited Hannah&amp;#39;s school teacher, 32yo Dan, to join in the fun. Now Dan comes for his second visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan&#39;s Idea For Little Hannah</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4627/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4627/</guid>
      <description>This is the 9th part of the Paedophile Ring series. Sean is a 35yo guy who lives with a single Mum, for the purpose of sexually abusing her pretty 9yo daughter. Hannah&amp;#39;s 32yo school teacher, Daniel Hall, has become complicit in the fun. This is his 2nd visit to see Hannah, and he clearly has &amp;#39;plans&amp;#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Putting 9-Year-Old Hannah To Bed</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4604/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4604/</guid>
      <description>This is the 7th story in the Pedophile Ring series, but can be read separate. Sean is a 35yo guy who lives with a single Mum, for the purpose of sexually abusing her pretty 9yo daughter. He has just &amp;#39;branched out&amp;#39; by inviting Hannah&amp;#39;s schoolteacher, 32yo Dan, to join in the fun. It now comes to the end of Dan&amp;#39;s first visit, and he had a &amp;#39;nice idea&amp;#39; to cap it off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing 9-Year-Old Hannah</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4565/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4565/</guid>
      <description>This is the story 6 in the Pedophile Ring series. Here, Hannah&amp;#39;s schoolteacher has taken up the invite to visit her and her stepdad abuser, and fulfill his own deeply illicit dreams with a child. Hannah is a pretty child, and one of his favourites in the class, so it is truly a dream come true for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Primary Teacher&#39;s Pedo Dream</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4551/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4551/</guid>
      <description>This is part 5 in the Pedophile Ring series. Sean is a 35yo guy and the live-in boyfriend of a pretty 9yo girl&amp;#39;s mother. He has one purpose in life for this arrangement, and now he has met &amp;#39;Dan&amp;#39; -Hannah&amp;#39;s schoolteacher - and it seems Dan also likes little girls in THAT way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
