<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>lolita on LS | Papermod</title>
    <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/tags/lolita/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lolita on LS | Papermod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/tags/lolita/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alexa and Uncle Jim</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/brody7981/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/brody7981/</guid>
      <description>A man finds that his 13 year old niece has the hots for him and she is actively trying to seduce him. He can&amp;#39;t possibly give in can he? What would his wife think? Come along on this story to find out what happens to Jim and his hot little niece named Alexa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Girl-of-the-Month Club, Part 5</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/netman7990/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/netman7990/</guid>
      <description>The rich can buy anything in America. Knowing this, one clever entrepenuer started a service for gentlemen called The Girl-of-the-Month Club. For a fee, you could subscribe to have a different teen or preteen girl, delivered to your house for an overnight sexual fantasy. Each month you would receive a different girl, dressed to provide the fantasy. This is the story of one year in the life of Blake Winthope and how he enjoyed his subscription. Part 5 is about how May&amp;#39;s Child, The Teenage Slut, surprises him and his buddies at their monthly poker game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Girl-of-the-Month Club, Part 3</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/netman7952/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/netman7952/</guid>
      <description>The rich can buy anything in America. Knowing this, one clever entrepenuer started a service for gentlemen called The Girl-of-the-Month Club. For a fee, you could subscribe to have a different teen or preteen girl, delivered to your house for an overnight sexual fantasy. Each month you would receive a different girl, dressed to provide the fantasy. This is the story of one year in the life of Blake Winthope and how he enjoyed his subscription. Part 3 is about March&amp;#39;s Child, The Girl Scout and how he samples the twelve-year old&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;cookies&amp;#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Girl-of-the-Month Club, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/netman7934/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/netman7934/</guid>
      <description>The rich can buy anything in America. Knowing this, one clever entrepenuer started a service for gentlemen called The Girl-of-the-Month Club. For a fee, you could subscribe to have a different teen or preteen girl, delivered to your house for an overnight sexual fantasy. Each month you would receive a different girl, dressed to provide the fantasy. This is the story of one year in the life of Blake Winthope and how he enjoyed his subscription. Part 2 is about February&amp;#39;s Child, The Cheerleader. Fourteen-year-old Wendy gives Blake a new appreciation of the splits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony &amp; Jessica, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/tandad7932/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/tandad7932/</guid>
      <description>This continues the loving adventures of Tony and his 9yo daughter Jessica after the death of his wife, Sara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etudes</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/benbad7907/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/benbad7907/</guid>
      <description>A young girl studies the arts of music and sex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Sister&#39;s Daughter, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/tommyknocker7895/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/tommyknocker7895/</guid>
      <description>Lee and uncle Tommy continue the game in the bedroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy For Sale</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/speedy7866/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/speedy7866/</guid>
      <description>Daniel has just arrived in Thailand for work. 9 year old Achara has candy for sale and a whole lot more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Jo</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/brody7859/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/brody7859/</guid>
      <description>A young girl&amp;#39;s mother leaves. She becomes a tomboy. This story is her sexual awaken and her becoming a young lady with desires for a neighbor boy and then her dad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony &amp; Jessica, Part 1</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/tandad7850/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/tandad7850/</guid>
      <description>A newly widowed father can no longer resist his daughter; they become lovers and embark on many horny adventures together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kate Versus the Zombies, Part 1</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/chrisjorgenson7611/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/chrisjorgenson7611/</guid>
      <description>I know what Loliwood needs--more zombies! This story is about the mid-point in a much larger tale I&amp;#39;ve had bouncing around my brain for a few years now; here, we are introduced to eleven-year-old Kate, a skilled zombie killer and--this will surprise you to learn--a nymphomaniac. Self-proclaimed &amp;#39;dirtiest girl you&amp;#39;ve ever met.&amp;#39; This is part one of four parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Conquest, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/etheralphantasm6651/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/etheralphantasm6651/</guid>
      <description>The Conquest continues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daddy &amp; Daughter, Dinner &amp; Dance, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/earldevere3383/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/earldevere3383/</guid>
      <description>The pedosexual adventure continues with daughter and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darla&#39;s Big Break, Part 1B</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered3043/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered3043/</guid>
      <description>Having convinced her 15 year old brother to be her tutor, 8 year old Darla turns out to be a quick study, but their activities get more than their bodies going, and soon, almost without noticing, they are in the middle of a torrid love affair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darla&#39;s Big Break, Part 1A</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2995/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2995/</guid>
      <description>When little eight year old Darla meets a grown man called Jerry at the theater she doesn&amp;#39;t know he&amp;#39;s just struck out on his own to produce child porn independently, or that he&amp;#39;s looking for a girl just like her to be his star. And although he suspects it on first sight, Jerry can&amp;#39;t yet know exactly how perfect She is or how much her brother has done to prepare her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginger Learns Her Lesson</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2904/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2904/</guid>
      <description>Ginger Collins had been going around teasing all the older single men in the apartment complex. This smart assed little thirteen year old girl had been watching all kinds of internet porn, and she figured she knew how far she could push it without getting raped. Truth be told, she was pretty good at gauging how far she had to go with each man to get his dick hard, before skipping out. The little tease got off on it. She&amp;#39;d go home, and masturbate after leaving these men all hot, and bothered. She&amp;#39;d think about the bulges she was able to cause in these grown men, as she started rubbing her fingers over the top of her vagina. She imagined how horny they must be, and how they were probably jacking off right now thinking about her, as she flicked her fingers on either side of her tender clitoris. She&amp;#39;d rub her thumb over, and around her clit, stroking her lips with her fingers, as she thought about what that man&amp;#39;s hard, naked cock must look like. As she rubbed, and then penetrated her virginal hole with her middle finger, she&amp;#39;d think about how bad they must want to fuck her. Still working her clit with her thumb, as she got to fingering herself real good, she&amp;#39;d think about how magical it would be when she met the right boy, who would gently take her virginity, because they were in love. She would bring herself to orgasm while imagining that all the older men that she teased could see her making love to her perfect boy friend, and how jealous they&amp;#39;d be. As the last shudder would run through her, she&amp;#39;d picture them jacking off, and crying. Afterword, she would giggle at how easy it was to get away with teasing these men. The day she knocked on thirty year old Ryan Rynolds door, Ginger had every reason to think that she was about to get away with it again, but what she didn&amp;#39;t know was that Ryan knew all about her little hijinx, and he was ready to teach her a lesson she&amp;#39;d never forget.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
