<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>MMMMg on LS | Papermod</title>
    <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/tags/mmmmg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MMMMg on LS | Papermod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/tags/mmmmg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Year Pedo Games</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5760/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5760/</guid>
      <description>This is story 38 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the sexual molesting of her now 10yo daughter, Hannah. Over time, 7 other men have come into her life, and 4 other girls have featured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun and Games in the Pedo Ring</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5070/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5070/</guid>
      <description>This is story 30 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a useless single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the complete sexual molesting of her attractive daughter, Hannah. Since then, others have got involved, the earliest being 32yo Dan, her gentle schoolteacher, and the not-so-gentle 37yo Simon. This story follows on directly from &amp;#39;Group-night with 10-year-old Hannah&amp;#39;(12th Nov).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Group Night for 10yo Hannah</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4931/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4931/</guid>
      <description>This is story 29 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a useless single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the complete sexual molesting of her attractive daughter, Hannah. Five other men have gradually become involved with her since, to varying degrees, and two little girls are less regular characters: 10yo freckled English cutie Abigail &amp;amp; 6yo Isreali half-breed Camelia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Young Hannah&#39;s Team Night</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4890/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4890/</guid>
      <description>This is story 27 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a useless single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the complete sexual molesting of her attractive 10yo daughter, Hannah. Over time, 4 other men had become regular &amp;#39;acqaintances&amp;#39; of the youngster, and she has also just been experimentally prostituted on the streets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Girl Swap</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4829/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv4829/</guid>
      <description>This is story 22 in the Pedo Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a useless single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the complete sexual molesting of her then 9yo dau Hannah. Over time, Dan (32) who is Hannah&amp;#39;s schoolteacher has joined in, as has his old friend 65yo Bill, and an old pedo buddy of Sean&amp;#39;s -37yo Simon. Now Simon has concluded a deal with an old pedo contact, Anthony, for regular exchanges of Hannah with a 6yo ethnic girl named Camelia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
