<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>coer on LS | Papermod</title>
    <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/tags/coer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coer on LS | Papermod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/tags/coer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Miranda&#39;s Rites</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/benbad7908/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/benbad7908/</guid>
      <description>Little girl gets nabbed stealing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer&#39;s Camp-Out, Part 1</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/leonneath7882/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/leonneath7882/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s Jennifer&amp;#39;s 8th birthday, and she has her friends over. On a warm summer evening, the girls soon get too warm...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Master Child-Abuser At Work</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv7390/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv7390/</guid>
      <description>This is episode 3 in my spin-off from my long-running &amp;#39;pedo ring&amp;#39; series, which featured a rugged and fairly good-looking pedo called Sean and 9yo Hannah as the central characters. Now, he has had to start all over again. The first paragraph of each episode summarizes what&amp;#39;s gone on before, so can be enjoyed separately. Go to the first episode, &amp;#39;Ravenous Pedo, Available Little Girl&amp;#39;, for a fuller description of her, but there are little reminders of her looks here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mad Love For A 10-Year-Old Girl</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6184/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6184/</guid>
      <description>This is episode 46, where I begin to draw the pedo ring series to an end (by 50). Here we see how things pan out for one of the young girls who featured earlier on in the series, and one of the adult male members. This episode can be read alone, but check out &amp;#39;The Pedo Ring Series Summary Of Episodes&amp;#39; under my author name, englishperv, if you want the fuller picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Orgy Of Child Sex, Part 1</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv6020/</guid>
      <description>This is episode 42 in the Ring series. It can be read alone but follows on directly from #40 &amp;amp; #41, which give the fuller setting. All the episodes are loosely linked by the central premise of a pedo ring (see&amp;#39;summary of episodes&amp;#39; for full order). Sean here is the central male character, stepdad to the extremely sexed 10yo Hannah. As the title suggests, tonight some of the other young girls in the ring are included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 7-Year-Old Treasure</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5544/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5544/</guid>
      <description>This is story 36 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the sexual molesting of her then 9yo daughter, Hannah. Over time, 7 other men have come into her life, two of whom being his good friend Simon, and Anthony. The latter specializes in &amp;#39;little&amp;#39; girls, and has another to offer...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fucked Fiona at Fourteen</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5094/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/englishperv5094/</guid>
      <description>This is story 31 in the Ring series. Sean (35) was the original character, living with a useless single Mum, Michelle, his whole purpose being the complete sexual molesting of her attractive 10yo daughter, Hannah. Since then, others have got involved, the earliest being 32yo schoolteacher Dan, who is smitten with her. 37yo Simon &amp;#39;likes&amp;#39; her too, in his way. Now, a 14yo called Fiona has arrived...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Incident At Cherry Lake, Part 5</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2903/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2903/</guid>
      <description>After a tense confrontation with Jackie, Derick decides to do what he thought he&amp;#39;d been trying to avoid. Fuck her youngest daughter, little 12 year old Jessica, and this causes Jackie to relive some childhood memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Incident At Cherry Lake, Part 4</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2848/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2848/</guid>
      <description>As this incident spins out of control everyone begins having emotional reactions beyond anything they had expected, including Derick, and it becomes unclear where this is going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Incident At Cherry Lake, Part 3</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2782/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2782/</guid>
      <description>Although he tries to keep his hands off of his hostages, events conspire to once again force his hand, and his cock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Incident At Cherry Lake, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2725/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2725/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Who are you Mister?&amp;rdquo; the young girl asked as she slowly approached Derick in the semi-dark bed room.
Derick had broken in to rob the place, but had forgotten to lock the door, and been caught in the act by this girl.
He was so surprised by her presence that he couldn&amp;rsquo;t move, or say anything, but then as she got closer, she surprised him even more. She lifted her little dress, holding it up with her chin, and then reached down, pulling her panties to her knees, revealing her fat, hairless outer labia with her tight little slit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Incident At Cherry Lake, Part 1</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2696/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/ericthered2696/</guid>
      <description>Derick is a professional thief, but when he decides to take a working vacation to Cherry Lake, choosing Jackie, and her three daughters (Jill-14, Jenny-13, and Jessica-12) he ends up getting more than he bargained for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera</title>
      <link>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/eva723/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alchemist6174.github.io/hugo/posts/eva723/</guid>
      <description>What should a woman do when a pretty child wants her picture taken and she is so appealing and alone and there&amp;#39;s no one else around to help?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
